hankooktire.com 2018-03-29

# Privacy Policy | Hankook USA

### Article 1

#### General Provisions

1-1.Hankook Tire America Corp. (hereinafter referred to as the "Company", also refers to the Company's web site which is [www.hankooktire.com/us](http://www.hankooktire.com/us/)) is committed to protecting your privacy on the internet. We believe that it is important for you to know what we do with your personal information. When it comes to consumer data collected electronically, the Company will provide notice, choice, access and security in ways described below.

1-2.The Company has set up procedures necessary to revise the Privacy Policy for its continued improvement. In the event of a revision to the Privacy Policy, steps are taken to ensure that you can easily recognize the revision.

### Article 2

#### Scope of Collection of Personal Information

2-1.You can visit the Company’s web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. The Company will not collect any personal data about you (e.g., name, country and e-mail address) unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with it.  
There are portions of the web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. (e.g., Q&A and Register your tires)  
The servers of the Company’s web site collect page URLs and not the e-mail addresses. This information may be aggregated on a "no names" basis just to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, or pages viewed.

2-2.The Company does not collect personal information which poses an obvious risk of infringing upon your basic rights (race and ethnicity, ideology and beliefs, hometown and legal domicile, political inclination and criminal record, health conditions such as medical history, sex life, etc.). However, exceptions are made when the personal information to be collected is stipulated under laws or is directly related to and thus required to provide services, in which case your consent will be required.

### Article 3

#### Consent to Collection of Personal Information

3-1.The Company provides a process through which you may check on the check box related to the Privacy Policy upon Q&A and Register your tires. If you check on check box, you will be regarded as having consented to collection of personal information.

### Article 4

#### Purpose of Collecting and Using Personal Information

4-1.Your personal information such as your name and e-mail address that we collect is only used to provide you with certain information you request.  
Your tire information including personal information that we collect is only used to contact you in the event of a recall.

4-2.Domain name information that we collect is only used to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.

### Article 5

#### Period for Storing and Using Personal Information

5-1.The Company will not preserve your personal data any longer than it is necessary to achieve the goals for which it was collected or for the time period required by law.

### Article 6

#### Collection of Personal Information Through Cookies

6-1.Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a web site. Cookies are then sent back to the originating web site on each subsequent visit, or to another web site that recognizes that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a web site to recognize a user’s device.  
Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.  
For further information on cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

6-2.The Company’s web site uses cookies. You can find out more about cookies and how to control them below.  
By using the web site, you accept the use of cookies in accordance with this cookie policy. If you do not accept the use of these cookies, please disable them following the instructions in this cookie policy. 

The web site uses the following cookies: 

**Strictly necessary cookies.** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our web site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our web site. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet. This category of cookies cannot be disabled.  
**Analytical cookies.** They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our web site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our web site works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. These cookies do not collect information that can identify you. All the information that these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to improve how the web site works.  
Our web site uses Google Analytics cookies. Information collected by Google Analytics cookies will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United states of America in accordance with its privacy practices. To see and overview of privacy at Google and how this applies to Google Analytics, visit <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You may opt out of tracking by Google Analytics by visiting [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below:

Cookie Type Cookie Type | Cookie Name | Source | Purpose  
---|---|---|---  
Strictly necessary | JSESSIONID | Hankook | Maintains session  
renderid  
Analytical | _ga | Google Analytics | Used to distinguish users by Google Analytics  
_dc_gtm | Google Analytics | Used to help identify the visitors by either age, gender, or interests by DoubleClick - Google Tag Manager  
_gat | Google Analytics | Used to throttle request rate  
  
6-3.You may disable cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to disable all cookies (including strictly necessary cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the site.  
Disabling a cookie or category of cookie does not delete the cookie from your browser. You will need to do this separately within your browser.  
If you would like to make changes to your cookie settings, please go to the 'Options' or 'Preferences' menu of your browser. Alternatively, go to the 'Help' option in your browser for more details.

To learn more about the cookie settings for your browser, please select the links below:  

If you have disabled one or more analytical cookies, we may still use information collected from cookies prior to your disabled preference being set, however, we will stop using the disabled cookie to collect any further information.  
Except for strictly necessary cookies, all cookies will expire after two years.

### Article 7

#### Usage outside the Stated Purpose and Third Party Access

7-1.The Company uses your personal information within the scope stipulated in Article 4 of this Privacy Policy. Usage does not go beyond the said scope and personal information is not provided to other persons, companies or organizations.

7-2.The Company does not disclose your information to third parties for their own independent marketing or business purposes. However, the Company may disclose your information to the following entities:  
Affiliates. Your personal information may be shared to emFrontier Co., Ltd to facilitate work activities and provide services on behalf of us.  
Other Parties When Required by Law or as Necessary to Protect Our Services. There may be instances when we disclose your information to other parties:  
to comply with the law or respond to compulsory legal process (such as a search warrant or other court order);  
to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Services; and  
to protect the rights, property, or safety, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, or customers.  
Other Parties in Connection With Corporate Transactions. We may disclose your information to a third party as part of a merger or transfer, or in the event of a bankruptcy.  
Other Parties With Your Consent or At Your Direction. In addition to the disclosures described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties when you consent to or request such sharing.

### Article 8

#### International Transfer of Information

8-1.If you choose to provide us with personal information, the Company may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.  
If you are visiting from other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from your region’s law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to your region which does not have the same data protection laws as other countries.

### Article 9

#### Link Sites

9-1.The Company may provide you with links to web sites and data of other companies. As the Company does not have any control over external sites and data, it does not bear any responsibility nor guarantees the utility of services or data provided thereof. If you move to the page of another site by clicking on links included in the Company, you are advised to review the privacy policy of the newly visited site, as the privacy policy of the said site has no relation to the Company.

### Article 10

#### Transmission of Advertising Content

10-1.The Company does not transmit advertising content for the purpose of profit generation that runs counter to your explicit refusal to receive such content.

10-2.The Company does not transmit advertising content on media which are inappropriate for minors (youths aged 13 years or younger).

### Article 11

#### Technical and Management Measures to Protect Personal Information

11-1.When handling your personal information, the Company takes the following technical measures to prevent the loss, theft, leak, alteration and damage of such information in order to maintain security: Your personal information is protected by separate security measures including encrypted file and data transmissions or the use of the file lock function. Vaccine programs are used to prevent damage caused by computer viruses, and such programs are updated regularly. In the event of a sudden virus outbreak, the related vaccine is provided as soon as it becomes available to prevent infringement of personal information. Code algorithms have been adopted to enable safe transmission of personal information over networks, firewalls have been installed to protect against hacking and outside intrusion and intrusion blocking systems and weakness analysis systems are used in each server to maintain security.

### Article 12

#### Rights and Obligations of Users

12-1.The Company will do its utmost to protect your personal information, as stated in this Privacy Policy; however, the Company is not liable for incidents caused by your own error or basic risks of the Internet.

12-2.Along with the right for protection of your personal information, you have the obligation to protect yourself and not to infringe upon others' information.

### Article 13

#### Collection and Use of Information from Children Under the Age of 13

13-1.The Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use the web site. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register on the web site or send us any personal information.

### Article 14

#### Withdrawal of Consent for Collection, Use and Provision of Personal Information

14-1.The Company will take the necessary steps so that withdrawal of consent for personal information collection can be executed with greater ease compared to the methods for collecting personal information.

14-2.If you inquire, make any corrections or request deletion of your personal information, please go to "Q&A" on Customer Center and place your request.

### Article 15

#### Personal Information Officer and Personal Information Manager

15-1.The Company designates a personal information officer and a personal information manager to receive suggestions and handle complaints related to personal information. The personal information officer and the personal information manager are as follows.

[Personal Information Officer]   
Name: Koh Myoung-Soo   
Team: Information Strategy Team   
E-mail: kms@hankooktire.com 

[Personal Information Manager]   
Name: Yoon Seong-Ha   
Team: Corporate Communications Team   
E-mail : shayoon@hankooktire.com

### Article 16

#### Revision of this privacy policy

16-1.This Privacy Policy became effective on December 17, 2016. Any amendments will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Thus, please check this page periodically.
